Guide to the Mabou Mines Archive MSS.133
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IX: Video Recordings
  - Subseries B: Video Recordings - Originals
    - Lee Breuer and Bob Telson's The Warrior Ant, 1986; ID: 133.0308 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0308)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0899
    - Lee Breuer and Bob Telson's The Warrior Ant, 1986; ID: 133.0309 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0309)
    - Lee Breuer and Bob Telson's The Warrior Ant, 1986; ID: 133.0310 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0310)
    - Lee Breuer and Bob Telson's The Warrior Ant, 1986; ID: 133.0311 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0311)
    - Lee Breuer and Bob Telson's The Warrior Ant, 1986; ID: 133.0312 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0312)
    - The Warrior Ant-The Ant in Hell, 1988; ID: 133.0314 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0314)
    - Warrior Ant @ BAM, 1988; ID: 133.0315A (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0315A)
    - Warrior Ant Raw Footage, 1988; ID: 133.0316 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0316)
    - The Warrior Ant Acts II & III, 1988; ID: 133.0317 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0317)
    - Warrior Ant, 1988; ID: 133.0319 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0319)
    - Warrior Ant, 1988; ID: 133.0320 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0320)
    - Warrior Ant, 1988; ID: 133.0321 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0321)
    - Warrior Ant, 1988; ID: 133.0322 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0322)
    - The Warrior Ant, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0323 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0323)
    - The Warrior Ant Part III, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0324 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0324)
    - The Warrior Ant, Part 4 (The Ant in Hell), 1987; ID: 133.0326 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0326)
    - Warrior Ant support materials, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0327 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0327)
    - Worstward Ho, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0328 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0328)
    - Worstward Ho in Geneva, 1991; ID: 133.0329 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0329)
    - Worstward Ho!, 1995; ID: 133.0330 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0330)
      Video 8 mm
    - Worstward Ho, 1995; ID: 133.0331 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0331)
    - Worstward Ho, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0332 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0332)
    - Sister Suzie, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0333 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0333)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0902
    - Sister Suzie Cinema, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0334 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0334)
    - Jungle, 1st Hour, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0335 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0335)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0905
    - Jungle, 2nd Hour, ID: 133.0336 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0336)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0908
    - In the Jungle of the Cities @ The Public Theater, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0337 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0337)
    - Jungle Clip Reel, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0338 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0338)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0911
    - MahabharANTa (Mabou Minds) @ ASUW, ID: 133.0339 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0339)
    - The MahabharANTa @ Ontological Theater; @ Arts @ St. Ann's, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0340 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0340)
    - Company, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0342 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0342)
    - Tears Worktape, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0343 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0343)
    - Flow My Tears The Policeman Said, Boston, copy 1, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0344 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0344)
    - Flow My Tears, Show Tape 1 Master, 1988; ID: 133.0345 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0345)
    - Flow My Tears, Show Tape 2 Master, 1988; ID: 133.0346 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0346)
    - Flow My Tears, Doc. of Show 1, 1988; ID: 133.0347 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0347)
    - Flow My Tears, Doc. of Show 3 [Note: believed to be pt.2], 1988; ID: 133.0348 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0348)
    - Flow My Tears, Doc. of Show 2, 1988; ID: 133.0349 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0349)
    - The 1st 20 Years, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0350 (Box 158, Media ID: 133.0350)
    - The First 20 Years (rough edit), [n.d.]; ID: 133.0351 (Box 158, Media ID: 133.0351)
    - The First 20 Years (not for broadcast), [n.d.]; ID: 133.0352 (Box 158, Media ID: 133.0352)
    - The First 20 Years, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0353 (Box 158, Media ID: 133.0353)
    - Tokuma & ITVS (Sample Reel), [n.d.]; ID: 133.0354 (Box 158, Media ID: 133.0354)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0914
    - Cuts from Lear, In the Jungle of Cities, and Through the Leaves, ID: 133.0355 (Box 158, Media ID: 133.0355)
    - Cuts from Company, Worstward Ho, The First 20 Years, and Through the Leaves, ID: 133.0356 (Box 158, Media ID: 133.0356)
    - Clips from Hajj and Lear, ID: 133.0357 (Box 158, Media ID: 133.0357)
    - Hajj, Worstward Ho, Company, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0358 (Box 158, Media ID: 133.0358)
    - It's A Man's World, Cold Harbor, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0359 (Box 158, Media ID: 133.0359)
    - Saint and Football, Interviews Backstage, B-Beaver Animation, Children's Workshop, ID: 133.0360 (Box 158, Media ID: 133.0360)
    - Red House and B-Beaver cuts, ID: 133.0361 (Box 158, Media ID: 133.0361)
    - Through the Leaves and 10 cuts from Lear, ID: 133.0362 (Box 158, Media ID: 133.0362)
    - Compilation, music video [master], [n.d.]; ID: 133.0363 (Box 158, Media ID: 133.0363)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0917
    - Paper ephemera from videotapes, undated (Box 165)
    - ID: 133.0364 - 133.0381 (Box 166)
- Series X: Press
  Series X contains numerous published articles written about Mabou Mines. There are original newspaper clippings, photocopies of clippings, magazine and journal articles, press releases, production histories, programs, and other related material. The material is arranged chronologically by subject. The series is divided into three subseries. The first part of Subseries A comprises pieces written about Mthe abou Mines company generally, and the second half comprises press about the company's awards and nominations. Subseries B is made up of press about individual company members and associates. The members are listed first, alphabetically, followed by the associates. Subseries C, the bulk of Series X, contains press and other material related to Mabou Mines productions and productions associated with Mabou Mines. The Mabou Mines plays are listed first, alphabetically by title, followed by the related productions.
  When the collection was maintained by Mabou Mines, the newspaper reviews for some productions had been individually foldered and each given a rating based on its favorability. This rating system was expressed through the use of color-coded circle stickers attached to the tops of some folders. Rave reviews were given red or orange stickers, yellow stickers were for mixed reviews, and black were for negative reviews. Presumably, this enabled those working at Mabou Mines to quickly determine the general critical opinion of a given performance, and also served as a shortcut to finding reviews from which to pull quotes for press releases, advertisements, etc. This rating system was not retained when the collection was processed at Fales Library for the following reasons: (1) the researcher is better served if several reviews of a performance are collected into a single folder; (2) the rating system was not uniformly applied; (3) some colored stickers had fallen off before the series was processed; (4) a reader can distinguish a rave from a pan.
  Boxes stored offsite: Box 45 - Barcode: 31142042236045 Box 46 - Barcode: 31142042236052 Box 47 - Barcode: 31142042236060 Box 48 - Barcode: 31142042236078 Box 113 - Barcode: 31142042236193
  - Subseries A: General Press
    Articles and clippings about Mabou Mines generally are listed first, followed by published mentions of the company's many awards and nominations.
    - San Francisco Chronicle Jan 12, 1972 "Mabou Mines Troupe Between Art, Theater" by Paine Knickerbocker (Box 45, Folder 1650)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042236045
    - San Francisco Examiner Jan 12, 1973 "The Floor is Part of Their Act" by Stanley Eichelbaum, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 1650a)
    - New York magazine May 15, 1972 "Museum as Theater" by Barbara Rose (Box 45, Folder 1651)
    - The Drama Review June 1972 "Collective Creation" by Theodore Shank (Box 45, Folder 1652)
    - Ruby Cohen article, [1972] (Box 45, Folder 1653)
    - Ruby Cohen article draft, undated (Box 113, Folder 2343)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042236193
    - various publications Feb-Jun 1973 three articles (Box 45, Folder 1654)
    - Village Voice Dec 29, 1975 "Voice Vanguard" (Box 45, Folder 1655)
    - Alternative Theatre Jan-Feb, 1975-1976 "Mabou Mines: From Beckett to Breuer" by Diane Nardone (Box 45, Folder 1656)
    - Art Press International (Summer 1976) [French] (Box 113, Folder 2344)
    - New York Times May 1, 1977 "The Art of Mabou Mines" by Roger Copland (Box 45, Folder 1657)
    - Tel Quel (Fall 1977) "Theatre aux Etats-Unis" by Tom Bishop [French] (Box 113, Folder 2345)
    - Bunch Festival misc. press, 1977-1978 (Box 113, Folder 2346)
    - Theatre Crafts Mar/Apr 1978 "Where Conceptual and Performance Art Meet" by H. Merton Goldman (Box 45, Folder 1658)
    - Washington Review Apr 1978 (Box 45, Folder 1659)
    - Weekly Soho News (V.5 No.33) May 18-24, 1978 Mabou Mines: Putting on the Dog" by Tish Dace (Box 113, Folder 2347)
    - New York magazine Oct 9, 1978 "Off-Off and Running" by Alan Rich (Box 113, Folder 2348)
    - Village Voice Jun 4, 1979 "The Souls of Art Folks" by Richard Goldstein (Box 45, Folder 1660)
    - Daily News May 15, 1980 "Dodger Theater, Mabou Mines share roof" by Ernest Leogrande (Box 113, Folder 2349)
    - Showbill Dec 1980 "The Inventive Mabou Mines" by Erika Munk (Box 45, Folder 1661)
    - Soho News Apr 29, 1981 "Is Mabou Mines Plural or Singular?" by Robert Coe and Don Shewey (Box 45, Folder 1662)
    - Theater Communications Vol. 3 No. 2 (May 1981); Vol. 3 No. 5 (August 1981) (Box 113, Folder 2350)
    - Alternatives Théâtrales Oct 1981 (Box 45, Folder 1663)
    - [Japanese reviews] 2/20/81; 8/13/82; 9/10/82, 1981-1982 (Box 113, Folder 2351)
    - [Japanese publication], 1982 (Box 45, Folder 1664)
    - New York Times Mar 18, 1984 "The Theater's Avant-Garde Branches Out" by Mel Gussow (Box 45, Folder 1665)
    - Broadway Bill of Fare Apr 19, 1984 "Reflections in a Broken Mirror" by Bennett Lew (Box 45, Folder 1666)
    - American Theatre June 1984 "The Many Voices of Mabou Mines" by Don Shewey (Box 45, Folder 1667)
    - The Daily Yomiuri Aug 19, 1984 "MM Theater About Ideas" by RoseMary Safranek (Box 113, Folder 2352)
    - On Stage: New York Mar 1985 (Box 45, Folder 1668)
    - Back Stage Jun 28, 1985 "In Search of the Avant Garde" by Ronn Mullen (Box 45, Folder 1669)
    - Opera For the 80's and Beyond July 1985 (Box 45, Folder 1670)
    - American Theatre Nov 1986 (Box 113, Folder 2353)
    - West Side Spirit Jun 1, 1987 "Mabou Mines: Cerebral Experimental Theater" by Dianne Arndt (Box 45, Folder 1671)
    - New York Times Mar 20, 1987 "Mabou Mines Revivals in a Brief Chelsea Run" by Jeremy Gerard (Box 45, Folder 1672)
    - Village Voice Mar 24, 1987 "Mabou Mines Chelsea Season" (Box 113, Folder 2354)
    - Option: Music Alternatives May/June 1987 (Box 113, Folder 2355)
    - Performance-Management Vol XII No 1 (Spring 1987) (Box 113, Folder 2356)
    - Interview June 1988 "Mabou Mines" by James Rasenberger (Box 45, Folder 1673)
    - Back Stage July 14, 1989 "Artists in Charge: The Revival of the Actor-Manager" (Box 113, Folder 2357)
    - Theatre Times Vol 8 No 3, Apr 1989 "Are CoProductions the Wave of the Future?" by Mindy Levine (Box 113, Folder 2358)
    - Theater Week Jan 29, 1990 "Mabou Mines Turns Twenty" by Alexis Greene (Box 45, Folder 1674)
    - ELLE May 1990 "The State of Mines" by John Howell (Box 45, Folder 1675)
    - Village Voice Jan 1, 1991 re: Mabou Mines: The First Twenty Years at Grey Art Gallery (Box 45, Folder 1676)
    - New York Times "Tragedy is Rewriting Avant-Garde Agenda" by John Rockwell, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 2359)
    - Village Voice Apr 14, Apr 21, 1992 two articles (Box 45, Folder 1677)
    - American Theatre Dec 1992 "Hunkering Down with Mabou Mines" by Roger Downey (Box 45, Folder 1678)
    - American Theatre Dec 1992 "On a Visit with Puppets" by Stephen Haff (Box 45, Folder 1679)
    - New York Daily News Nov 20, 1993 "Avant Let Down Their Garde" by Lewis Beale (Box 45, Folder 1680)
    - Scena interviews with Akalaitis, Breuer, [1993] (Box 45, Folder 1681)
    - The New Yorker Oct 22, 1995 "An Uptown Girl at a Downtown Concert" by Miriam Lewin (Box 45, Folder 1682)
    - New York Times Jan 1, 1996 Heiner Muller obituary (Box 113, Folder 2360)
    - [Serbian press], undated (Box 113, Folder 2361)
    - photocopy of handwritten history of Mabou Mines (1957-1975) (Box 45, Folder 1683)
    - financial/funding articles, 1981-1990 (Box 45, Folder 1684)
    - Funding and theater press, 1980-1991 (Box 113, Folder 2362)
    - list of awards, 1974-1984 (Box 45, Folder 1685)
    - Obie Awards Jun 7, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 1686)
    - Obie Awards Jun 6, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 1687)
    - Obie Awards Jun 12, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 1688)
    - Villager Downtown Theater Awards Jul 27, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 1689)
    - Obie Awards May 28, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 1690)
    - Villager Downtown Theater Awards May 31, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 1691)
    - Obie Awards Jun 9, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 1692)
    - Villager Downtown Theater Awards, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 1693)
    - Obie Awards Jun 3-9, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 1694)
    - Villager Downtown Theater Awards Jun 11, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 1695)
    - Obie Awards May 31, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 1697)
    - Villager Downtown Theater Awards Jun 6, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 1698)
    - Maharam Stage Awards (in Variety) Jul 27, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 1699)
    - Maharam Design Prizes Variety, 10/12/83, 1983 (Box 113, Folder 2363)
    - Brandeis University Creative Arts Awards Apr 26, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 1700)
    - Obie Awards May 21, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 1701)
    - Obie Awards May 27, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 1702)
    - Obie Awards May 26, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 1703)
    - Obie Awards May 29, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 1704)
    - Village Voice Best of the '80s Jan 2, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 1705)
    - Village Voice May 30, 1995 "I Lost It At the Obies" by Ross Wetzsteon (Box 45, Folder 1706)
    - Obie Awards May 28, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 1707)
    - Obie Awards May 27, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 1708)
    - Misc. Villager Awards, 1978-1983 (Box 113, Folder 2364)
    - Misc. Obie Awards, 1976-1998 (Box 113, Folder 2365)
    - Misc. awards, N/A (Box 113, Folder 2366)
    - Misc. press and press-related files, N/A (Box 113, Folder 2367)
  - Subseries B: Company Members & Associates
    Articles and clippings about Mabou Mines company members are listed first, arranged alphabetically by last name, then chronologically. Some clippings about company associates are listed alphabetically following the last company member, Warrilow. This subseries includes some curricula vitae in addition to press items.
    - Akalaitis, various publications, 1977-1979 (Box 45, Folder 1710)
    - Akalaitis, Village Voice, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 1711)
    - Akalaitis, "Jane Bowles" program, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 1712)
    - Akalaitis, Christian Science Monitor, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 1713)
    - Akalaitis, New York magazine, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 1714)
    - Akalaitis, various publications, re: "Request Concert", 1981 (Box 45, Folder 1715)
    - Akalaitis, various publications, May-Jun 1981, re: "Request Concert" (Box 45, Folder 1716)
    - Akalaitis, Time, Oct 5, 1981 w/ the famous "JoAnne Akalaitis' Mabou Mines" line' (Box 45, Folder 1717)
    - Akalaitis, various publications, Feb-Mar 1981, re: "Request Concert" (Box 45, Folder 1718)
    - Akalaitis, various publications, Nov 1981, re: "Dark Ride" (Box 45, Folder 1719)
    - Akalaitis, various publications, May 1982, re: "Red and Blue" [includes press release] (Box 45, Folder 1720)
    - Akalaitis, Theatre Communications, Jan 1983 (Box 45, Folder 1721)
    - Akalaitis, New York Times Magazine, May 1, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 1722)
    - Akalaitis, In Performance, Oct 1983 (Box 45, Folder 1723)
    - Akalaitis various publications Oct-Dec 1983 (Box 45, Folder 1724)
    - Akalaitis Theatre Journal May 1984 "Some Versions of Performance Art" by Xerxes Mehta (Box 113, Folder 2368)
    - Akalaitis Back Stage Jul 20, 1984 re: Maharam Awards (Box 45, Folder 1725)
    - Akalaitis various publications Nov-Dec 1984 re: Beckett's "Endgame" (Box 45, Folder 1726)
    - Akalaitis various publications Jan-Mar 1985 re: Beckett's "Endgame" (Box 45, Folder 1727)
    - Akalaitis various publications Jul-Sep 1985 (Box 45, Folder 1728)
    - Akalaitis Village Voice Feb 25, 1986 re: "The Balcony" (Box 45, Folder 1729)
    - Akalaitis various publications May-Jun 1986 re: "Green Card" (Box 45, Folder 1730)
    - Akalaitis Minneapolis Star Tribune Oct 18, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 1731)
    - Akalaitis various publications Feb, Jun-Jul 1988 (Box 45, Folder 1732)
    - Akalaitis New York Times, NY Daily News Jun 1, 1989 re: "Cymbeline" (Box 45, Folder 1733)
    - Akalaitis various publications Nov-Dec 1989 re: "The Screens" (Box 45, Folder 1734)
    - Akalaitis NYTW News Winter 1995 (Box 45, Folder 1735)
    - Akalaitis The Drama Review NYU/School of the Arts, undated (Box 45, Folder 1736)
    - Akalaitis / Breuer [Italian interview], undated (Box 113, Folder 2369)
    - Breuer biographies and curricula vitae, 1981-1995 (Box 45, Folder 1737)
    - Breuer San Francisco Examiner Jan 12, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 1738)
    - Breuer Village Voice Dec 29, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 1739)
    - Breuer Village Voice Jun 12, 1978 re: Obies (Box 45, Folder 1740)
    - Breuer (author) Village Voice Mar 5, 1979 "A Modest Proposal" (Box 45, Folder 1741)
    - Breuer The Scene Aug 1, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 1742)
    - Breuer Oct 1, 1979 bibliography of articles about Breuer/Mabou Mines (Box 45, Folder 1743)
    - Breuer "An interview with Lee Breuer" by Richard J. Stayton, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 1744)
    - Breuer various publications Mar, Aug 1980 (Box 45, Folder 1745)
    - Breuer Reader (LA free weekly) Aug 29, 1980 interview (Box 45, Folder 1746)
    - Breuer various publications Mar, Jun 1981 re: "Lies" (Box 45, Folder 1747)
    - Breuer various publications Mar, Summer/Fall 1981 re: "Lulu" (Box 45, Folder 1748)
    - Breuer Santa Cruz Express Apr 8, 1981 interview (Box 45, Folder 1749)
    - Breuer various publications Jun-Jul 1981 re: "The Tempest" [includes program, press release] (Box 45, Folder 1750)
    - Breuer Soho News Jul 1, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 1751)
    - Breuer (author) Soho News Feb 2, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 1752)
    - Breuer various publications Feb 5, 1982 re: "Red Beads" (Box 45, Folder 1753)
    - Breuer Observer Aug 28, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 1754)
    - Breuer various publications "Warrior Ant", 1985-1991 (Box 45, Folder 1755)
    - Breuer New York Times Sep 6, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 1756)
    - Breuer ELLE Oct 1988 (Box 45, Folder 1757)
    - Breuer In Their Own Words: Contemporary American Playwrights interview by David Savran, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 1758)
    - Breuer The Star-Ledger Sep 19, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 1759)
    - Breuer Greek interview, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 1760)
    - Breuer (author) Village Voice Aug 20, 1991 "The Two-Handed Gun" (Box 45, Folder 1761)
    - Breuer New Times Dec 11-17, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 1762)
    - Breuer (author), SPAN, Aug 1992, "Playing to the Flame" (Box 45, Folder 1763)
    - Breuer (author), Performing Arts Journal no 1, "How We Work", undated (Box 45, Folder 1764)
    - Breuer, miscellaneous press, undated (Box 45, Folder 1765)
    - Breuer, unidentified clipping, undated (Box 45, Folder 1766)
    - Glass various publications, 1986-1986 (Box 45, Folder 1767)
    - Malaczech interview agreement [w/ photocopied drawing and unidentified 2-pg. story], 1977 (Box 113, Folder 2370)
    - Maleczech Performance Art no 2, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 1768)
    - Maleczech New York magazine Feb 23, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 1769)
    - Maleczech The Independent Oct 1983 (Box 45, Folder 1770)
    - Malaczech various publications, 1983 (Box 113, Folder 2371)
    - Maleczech various publications Oct 1984 (Box 45, Folder 1771)
    - Maleczech Village Voice Jul 9, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 1772)
    - Maleczech various publications, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 1773)
    - Maleczech Theater Week Dec 14-20, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 1774)
    - Maleczech various publications May, Dec 1988 re: "Life and Fate" [includes program] (Box 45, Folder 1775)
    - Maleczech New York Newsday Dec 7, 1988 interview (Box 45, Folder 1776)
    - Maleczech various publications, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 1777)
    - Maleczech High Performance Spring 1990 (Box 45, Folder 1778)
    - Maleczech American Theatre April 1992 (Box 45, Folder 1779)
    - Maleczech miscellaneous press [incl. photograph, press-related correspondence, etc.], undated (Box 45, Folder 1780)
    - Neumann biographies, 1993, undated (Box 45, Folder 1781)
    - Neumann various publications, 1981-1995 (Box 45, Folder 1782)
    - O'Reilly biographies with contracts for "Ironweed", 1987, undated (Box 45, Folder 1783)
    - O'Reilly biographies, undated (Box 45, Folder 1784)
    - Raymond various publications, 1984, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 1785)
    - Warrilow unidentified clipping, [1972-1973] (Box 46, Folder 1786)
    - Warrilow various publications Dec 1979-Nov 1980 re: Beckett's "A Piece of Monologue" [includes program], 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 1787)
    - Warrilow various publications Jan, Mar 1982 (Box 46, Folder 1788)
    - Warrilow New York Times Feb 6, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 1789)
    - Warrilow various publications Jun-Jul 1983 re: "Ohio Impromptu" (Box 46, Folder 1790)
    - Warrilow New York Times Sep 24, 1984 re: Beckett's "All Strange Away" (Box 46, Folder 1791)
    - Warrilow New York Times Nov 22, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 1792)
    - Warrilow American Theatre Apr 1989 (Box 46, Folder 1793)
    - Warrilow, various publications, Aug-Dec 1995, obituaries (Box 46, Folder 1794)
    - Warrilow, calendar, undated (Box 46, Folder 1795)
    - Jill Godmilow, curriculum vitae, [1983-1984] (Box 46, Folder 1796)
    - Karen Kandel, unidentified publication, re: "Peter and Wendy", undated (Box 46, Folder 1797)
    - Al Kryszak, curriculum vitae, undated (Box 46, Folder 1798)
    - Mark Morris, various publications, Mar-Apr 1986 (Box 46, Folder 1799)
    - Lute Ramblin' (Breuer), curriculum vitae, [1986-1987] (Box 46, Folder 1800)
  - Subseries C: Productions
    Articles and clippings about Mabou Mines productions are listed first, arranged alphabetically by title, then chronologically. Articles and other material about Mabou Mines-related productions are listed next. The designation "Beckett Plays" refers to any combination of Come and Go, The Lost Ones, and Play, which were often performed together in the company's early days. The company used this designation for the numerous published items that mention one or all of these plays, and it was retained for this series. Please note, however, that in other series each production is referred to by its individual title.
    - Beckett plays / Red Horse Animation Minnesota Daily Nov 5, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 1801)
    - Beckett plays unidentified publication [Jan 1972] Berkeley performance (Box 46, Folder 1802)
    - Beckett plays / Red Horse Animation Vogue Jul 1972 (Box 46, Folder 1803)
    - Beckett plays various publications, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1804)
    - Beckett plays Alternative Theatre Jan-Feb 1975-1976 (Box 46, Folder 1805)
    - Beckett plays various publications Germany, Italy, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 1806)
    - Beckett plays scrapbook of phototcopied Italian clippings given to Akalaitis, Aug 25, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 1807)
    - Beckett plays various publications, 1976-1978 (Box 46, Folder 1808)
    - Beckett plays various publications Jan 1979 French reviews of "The Lost Ones" (Box 46, Folder 1809)
    - Beckett plays various publications France, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 1810)
    - Beckett plays On Stage New York (Italian) Oct 1985 (Box 46, Folder 1811)